Hello everyone, ICC Lombard has made a major change to provide
better claim services to its policy holders. This is the
first change in the health insurance industry regarding claim services. This
means that no health
insurance company has made this change before.
If you want to know which
claim services change can
provide huge benefits to the policy holder, then
watch this video completely because at the
end of the video, we will also
tell you that if you make some mistakes, you will
not get the claim. I, Ajeeb
Sehrawat, welcome you to our channel.
On this channel, we regularly share information regarding insurance and
investment.
If you have any questions, you
can ask in the comments section. If you
like our videos, then like the video
and definitely subscribe to the channel so that
you keep getting such useful information on a regular basis.
If you
want to invest in the stock market, then there are links to some
important companies like Ab Stock J Fund
Bazaar
in the description. By clicking on them, you
can open your account and invest.  You
can start, so let's start the video. The
change that ICC Lombard has made is that
if you have a paralyzing surgery, that is,
you have to undergo any paralyzing treatment, then
you can
intimate ICC Lombard 24 hours in advance and avail cashless treatment at any hospital that is
not on their cashless panel. This is
a
huge change because many
hospitals are not on the company's panel list.
If the policyholder gets treatment at those hospitals, then the
policyholder first has to
pay out of his pocket.
Now I have to file for reimbursement claim,
which is a lengthy process,
plus the policyholder has to
pay out of his pocket. But
after adding this service, the policyholder can
go to any hospital and avail cashless facility,
which is a huge benefit for the policyholder.
Before using these services, you need to keep a few points in mind.
First, you need to inform the company 24 hours in advance,
which
you can process through their MillTechCare app. The
first process is to
log in to your MillTechCare app.  Then
after that click on the service offer option,
after that click on health assistant
and the fourth step is
you can intimate the company by clicking on Anywhere Cashless,
other points are that this
benefit is available only on free plain surgery,
right now
these services are not available for emergency and accidental situations and the
third and biggest point is that if you
visit a hospital which is
in the blacklist of the company, that is, if that
hospital has been blacklisted by the company, then
if you get treatment in that hospital, then the company will
not pay your claim, so this was a
big change which ICC Lombard has done to
provide good services to its policy holders,
which is a very good change,
like and subscribe, if you liked the video then
finally thank you for watching